shopvisible.com 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy - Hosted Ecommerce Software | ShopVisible

We are ShopVisible, LLC and its affiliates (“ **ShopVisible** ”). Welcome to our website.

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting any personal information you share with us through this website. This privacy policy statement (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) explains how we collect personal information about you through this website and how this information is then used or disclosed. It does not apply to those of our websites that do not display or link to this Privacy Policy or that have their own Privacy Policy or to information we may collect from you or about you in other ways, including through emails you may send to us. This Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any party.

Residents of the State of California, please also read [Your California Privacy Rights](http://www.shopvisable.com/California-Privacy-Policy.asp "California Privacy Policy") to understand additional rights you may have pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83.

Generally, we gather information about you to provide you with convenient access to certain features and services, verify your identity in our interactions with you, to communicate offers on products and services that we believe will be of interest to you, to deliver a better customer service experience, to administer our business, and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy and on our website. For example, to access certain of our features, services, and non-public areas of our website, you will be asked to sign in with a login name and password. If you choose not to provide us with the requested information, you will not be able to access such non-public areas because we cannot verify your identity. Your information also helps us keep you posted on status updates, reminders, confirmations, and special offers, and events that may interest you.

We hope that this Privacy Policy will remove any concerns you may have about supplying us with information and make visiting this website a rewarding and safe experience. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting the updated terms on this website. You are responsible for periodically reading this Privacy Policy. If you use this website after we have updated this Privacy Policy, you acknowledge that you have read the updated terms and consent to our privacy practices. This Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any person. This website is not directed to children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13 years of age.

**Personal Information We Collect and Use Through This Website**

We define “personal information” as information that is unique to you and may include your phone number, name, age, address, Social Security number or credit card number. We do not collect any personal information about you through this website unless you choose to provide it to us voluntarily. If you do provide us with personal information, we will only use it for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or where it is collected. If you encounter a screen or page that requests information you do not want to share with us, do not enter the information and do not proceed with that screen or page.

If you register with us, we will collect name, address, phone number, email address. Generally, we use this information to respond to, process, and fulfill your requests, and update you on status. When you purchase products and services, we will require that you provide payment and other necessary information required by our third-party providers, including billing information. Other examples of when we may ask you to provide personal information include if you subscribe to receive updates, choose to provide us with your preference information (such as interests, product preferences, and items purchased) so that we can suggest products and search results that may be of interest to you. Finally, we may also use your postal mail or email address or phone number to send you further information about ShopVisible or to contact you for the purposes of research, product development, or customer service. We may also aggregate personal and other information about you collected from this website with other information you provide us through interactions with you through the telephone or otherwise.]

We will not sell, license, transmit or disclose your personal information outside of ShopVisible unless: (1) you expressly authorize us to do so; (2) it is necessary to enable third-party providers of products and services available on this website to respond to, process and fulfill your requests; (3) it is necessary to allow our trusted service providers or agents to provide services for us; (4) in order to provide our products or services to you; (5) it is in connection with a sale of all or substantially all of the assets of ShopVisible or of [www.shopvisible.com](http://www.shopvisible.com/) (or any other division of ShopVisible with substantial connection to the personal information) or the merger of ShopVisible into another entity or any consolidation, share exchange, combination, reorganization, or like transaction in which ShopVisible is not the survivor; or (6) otherwise as we are required or permitted by law.

We will not disclose your personal information to a third party for their direct marketing purposes unless you first affirmatively agree to the disclosure.

**Cookies and Other Automated Means of Collecting Information**

As is true of most websites, we gather technical information about your interaction with our website automatically, and store it in our logs. Such information includes Internet Protocol addresses, web browser type, host or service provider, referring or exit pages, operating system, and date and time stamps.  
And, as is true of most websites, we use “cookies” – files that are sent to your browser and stored on your personal computer. Cookies are commonly used by online services to improve the user experience and have not been known to transmit computer viruses or otherwise harm your computer. Many cookies last only through a single website session, or visit. Others may have an expiration date, or may remain on your computer until you delete them. Our cookies will track only your activity relating to your online activity on this website, and will not track your other Internet activity. You can decide if and how your computer will accept a cookie by configuring your preferences or options in your browser. However, if you choose to reject cookies, you may not be able to use or access certain pages of this website or certain of our features, products or services.

We may occasionally use other companies to set cookies on our website and gather cookie information for us. In some cases, we may also use another company to operate web servers or process credit card purchases for our website. We use the cookie information gathered by these companies in the same manner as stated above.  
In some cases, we retain both the cookie information and/or the information you provide to us online – for example, to complete a transaction you requested or to keep historical records of your past transactions. In other cases, we only retain the cookie and/or online information you give us if you request us to do so for your use in subsequent sessions.

Finally, we may also use very small electronic images, known as “web beacons” from us and third parties to identify your interaction with our and such third-party websites over time.

By way of example, we may use automated means of collecting information 

  1. to provide you with a more customized experience on our website and provide you greater convenience each time you interact with us,
  2. to make it easier for you to use different parts of our website without having to login multiple times,
  3. to help us understand which parts of our website are the most popular and how much time our users spend in each,
  4. to store your preferences for certain kinds of information and marketing offers,
  5. to measure the effectiveness of our communications, promotional campaigns, and the searches performed on our website,
  6. to administer our website,
  7. to develop statistics on any advertisements displayed on our websites, and
  8. to study aggregate demographic information about our users as a whole.

**Protecting Your Personal Information**  

We restrict access to personal information collected about you through our website to our employees, our affiliates’ employees, or others who need to know this information to provide services to you or in the course of administering and conducting our business. We maintain appropriate physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information. We protect our database with various physical, technical and procedural measures and we restrict access to your information by unauthorized persons. We also advise our employees about their responsibility to protect customer information and we provide them with appropriate guidelines for adhering to our business ethics standards and policies.

You can also help us protect your personal information by

  1. using only secure web browsers,
  2. employing common anti-virus and anti-malware tools on your system to keep it safe,
  3. carefully logging out after using our website,
  4. using strong password with a combination of letters and numbers,
  5. changing your password often, and
  6. notifying us by email at support@shopvisible.com if you feel your login and/or password have been compromised.

Finally, please exercise discretion and use caution with respect to your personal information. We may provide public areas on our website where you can post information about yourself and others. We do not control who reads postings on our website, or how they may use or disclose such information. If you choose to voluntarily disclose personal information on public portions of our website, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages.

**Updating and Verifying Information We Have About You**

If you are a registered user, you can review and maintain your account information at anytime, by logging in to your account or submitting a request to support@shopvisible.com. In addition, you may request a copy of the information that we currently hold about you by sending a detailed email to support@shopvisible.com with all specifics necessary for us to consider and respond to your request.

**Third Parties**

This website may contain links to third-party websites. While we endeavor to work with third-parties that share our respect for user privacy, we are not responsible for the websites or privacy practices of such third-parties. We do not endorse these parties, their content, or any products and services they offer. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such websites. You are responsible for knowing when you are leaving our website to visit a third-party website, and for reading and understanding the terms of use and privacy policy statements for each such third-party website.

**Terms of Use**

Please read our [Terms of Use] to understand the terms that apply to your use of this website. By using this website, you acknowledge that you have read our terms of use and this Privacy Policy, and agree to comply with them.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [communications@shopvisible.com](mailto:communications@shopvisible.com). You can also reach us by regular mail at:  
ShopVisible, LLC  
945 East Paces Ferry Road  
Suite 1475  
Atlanta, GA 30326 USA
